天啊 居然有顾客上门
Oh, my God! We have customers?
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
怎么来了这么多嬉皮士啊
Why are there so many hipsters here?
我们开始卖傻逼帽子
Are we selling stupid hats and telling them
然后乱夸他们超有才吗
they're more talented than they actually are?
不 那种店早有了 就是那家装潮帽店啊
No, that's already a store. It's called "Fedorable."
你一直很努力地帮店里招揽顾客
You've been working so hard to get us customers in,
所以我也想找到个方法
I wanted to contribute by finding a way
来招揽跟这一带的嬉皮士
to get in the neighborhood hipsters.
这就是我们的新传单
So... here's our new flyer.
你问都没问我 就弄个新传单啊
You made up a new flyer without talking to me about it first?
我给小蛋糕都冠上90年代的名人名呢
I renamed all the cupcakes after people from the '90s!
"麦克斯自制小蛋糕
"Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
所有你们要的"口味哥"都有"
We've got all your Flavor Flavs."
嬉皮士爱回忆90年代
Hipsters love '90s nostalgia more than they love
更胜假装自己啥都不爱
pretending not to love anything.
欢迎来舔舔"瘪四"小蛋糕
"Come in and lick a Beavis.
或吃个"大头蛋"
Eat a butt-head."
开心果小蛋糕现在改叫"丹尼斯·罗德曼"
The pistachio is now called the Dennis Rodman
这蠢蛋糕就得用蠢货的名
because it's such a dumbass flavor.
真不错
Cute.
等等 那边怎么回事
Wait, what's going on over there?
那些小蛋糕怎么都烂兮兮的
Why are all those cupcakes smashed?
那些是"南茜·克里根"小蛋糕
Those are the Nancy Kerrigans.
拿她的惨事当笑点
I don't know if it's in good taste
会不会有点太无下限啊
to make fun of her personal tragedy.
-都卖掉八个了呢 -管她去死 你就是个天才
- I sold eight of them. - Screw her, you're a genius!
可以让我也取一个吗
Ooh, ooh, can I name one?
我可以把隔夜的小蛋糕取为"休·海夫纳"吗
How 'bout we call the day-olds the Hugh Hefners?
他又不90年代
That's not '90s.
但他90多岁 如隔夜蛋糕般"又老又硬"
He's in his 90s, and he's stale and hard.
我要外带一个"乔纳森·泰勒·托马斯"
Can I get a Jonathan Taylor Thomas to go
再加任意两个"辣妹"
and two of the Spice Girls?
但我不要"宝贝辣妹"哦
Any one but "Baby."
没问题
Sure.
兄台 你应该来参加九十年代冷知识大赛
Dude, you should come to the '90s trivia contest
每周一在"酒吧"吧举行哦
every Monday at the Bar bar.
你能赢一大笔钱呢
You could win, like, big money.
赢一大笔钱来支付我为了忘掉
Yeah, and then I could pay for the lobotomy I'd need
参加过酒吧里的嬉皮士蠢赛
to forget that I ever participated
而去施行的脑部手术吗
in a hipster contest in a bar.
您帽子好有爱 又好有才华哦
Cute hat. You're very talented.
我去把这传单贴我们窗子上吧
I'm putting this flyer up in the window.
你看 咱店门口有个街头艺人
Oh, look, there's a street performer trying to get people
想拉路人跟他的牵线木偶跳舞
to dance with his marionette outside our shop.
这可不行
Uh-oh, not cool!
嬉皮士才不会想跟木偶跳小丑舞呢
No hipster wants to krump with a puppet.
你看 把客人都吓跑了
See, he just chased them away.
我们请他去别地方就行了 要友善哦
We'll just ask him to move, but we have to be nice.
什么友善 友善...
Nice? Nice...
就是趁我妈在卧室藏新买的电视机时
Oh, yeah, that's the thing you are to the welfare lady
而我要对那位发补助金的女士装穷扮可怜的样子吗
while your mom's in the bedroom hiding the new TV.
您好吗 我们是这小蛋...
Hi, how are you? We own this cupcake--
安静 他在跳舞呢
Shh! Not while he's dancing.
抱歉了 您是想我等他跳完吗
I'm sorry, would you like me to wait?
这家伙绝对是变态杀人魔
Oh, this dude's a serial killer.
您是想我...
Do you want me to...
绝对是杀人魔
Yup, total serial killer.
我们俩早晚会成为他地下室里的
Just a matter of time till we're hung on strings
真人牵线偶
in his basement.
而且我估计还染上了木偶疱疹
And I probably just got puppet herpes.
希望您还喜欢
Well, I hope you enjoyed your kiss
与万人迷皮埃尔的那个吻
with Charming Pierre.
如果您赏脸的话...
Now, if you wouldn't mind...
原来皮埃尔是牛郎啊
Oh, Pierre's a prostitute?
他在大庭广众之下就"开工" 有点怪吧
It's a little weird for him to do it out in the open,
他要买不起车当"工作站" 那也没办法
but if he can't afford a car, he can't afford a car.
看来你是那种没好奇心的无趣女人
Oh, you're one of those-a woman without wonder.
才不是呢 我现在就很好奇
Not true. In fact, I'm wondering
你怎么赚得到房租钱
how you manage to pay rent.
你们能哪儿凉快哪待去吗
Okay, could you two just move along?
我五分钟后要开始下一场演出了
I have another show in five minutes.
那也算是演出啊
That was a show?
听好 不许在这表演你的把戏
Look, you can't do your little skits here.
她其实没有负面的意思啦
She doesn't mean to be negative.
她说得对 我本来也打算给点正面评价
She's right. I was planning to be all positive
但你的娃娃强奸她腿后就没了
till your doll raped her leg.
皮埃尔不是娃娃好吗
Pierre is not a doll, okay?
他是个牵线木偶 我亲手雕刻的呢
He is a marionette. Hand-carved by me.
而且我表演的也不是"把戏" 懂吗
And I don't do "skits," Okay?
我的演出还得到国家的赞助呢
I received a national endowment for my work.
什么 政府花钱补助这种玩意儿
What? The government pays for stuff like this,
而我连补大牙的钱都没
and I can't get my back tooth fixed?
我个人呢 是真的很欣赏
Well, I, for one, really appreciate
木偶戏的艺术啦
the art of puppetry.
我看得出来 而且...
I can tell you do, and...
皮埃尔也看得出
so can Pierre.
他可不会随便亲近人呢
You know, he doesn't just approach anybody.
我叫卡洛琳 她是麦克斯 你是...
I'm Caroline. This is Max. And you are?
我的艺名叫"劫佩托"
My stage name is J. Petto.
真有爱 小木偶的爸爸"杰佩托"嘛
Oh, so cute. Geppetto, like Pinocchio's father.
不 是"劫"佩托
No, it's "J," period, "Petto."
迪士尼公司有"杰佩托"这名字的版权
Disney owns the rights to the name Geppetto,
所以可怜的街头艺人只能屈服于淫威之下啦
so once again, the poor, starving artist gets screwed!
真可怜 你能走吗
So sad. Can you move?
你看 这是我们的小蛋糕店
See, this is our cupcake shop,
你挡住了我们的门口
and you're blocking the entrance.
这里是公共区域
Uh, this is a public space,
我知道我有哪些公民权利
and I know my rights.
表演开始
Showtime!
我刚才一直试着对你友善
I was trying to be nice,
但你是我见过最没礼貌的操偶师
but you are the rudest puppeteer I've ever met.
比莎里·刘易斯这个
And I'm including Shari Lewis,
在我五岁生日派对上 叫我老爸吃屎的人还无礼
who told my father to shove it on my fifth birthday!
走吧 麦克斯
Let's go, Max.
喂 娃娃男
Hey... Doll man.
惹龙惹凤也别惹我们
You don't want to mess with us.
我给警察打个电话
I make one call to the cops,
他们调查一下你的背景 我肯定很快
they do a background check, and I'm pretty sure you'd go
就能查出你恋童癖的事哦
from "J. Petto" to "J. Petto-Phile."
小姐 我把"大卫·霍索夫"弄掉地上了
Miss, I dropped my David Hasselhoff.
这也不是他第一次倒在地上了
Well, it's not the first time he's been on the floor.
不许你这么说我
Hey, you can't talk to me like that.
我曾经就学于巴黎学习木偶艺术...
I studied puppetry in Paris at the palais--
天啊 他踩到"大卫·霍索夫" 滑倒了
Oh, my God, he slipped on David Hasselhoff!
-你没事吧 -没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
我没事 没事啦
Yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine.
觉得有点丢脸而已
I'm just a little embarrassed.
惨了 惨了 我压在皮埃尔身上了
Oh, no, no. I landed on Pierre!
皮埃尔
Pierre?
来 请坐
Here, have a seat.
你要喝杯咖啡还是来个免费小蛋糕吗
Would either of you like a coffee or a free cupcake?
不用 我收拾一下就走 谢谢
No, I'm just gonna pack up and go. Thank you.
随时欢迎回来吃免费小蛋糕
Come back anytime for a free cupcake.
不过娃娃就不必带着了
But no need to bring your dolls.
这不是娃娃好吗 我是个男人
They're not dolls! I'm a man!
我们的新传单发出去后
It's crazy how many hipsters
今天来店里光顾的嬉皮士超级多
came into our shop today from our new flyers.
而且店里所有的
We ran completely out of all
花生巧克力小蛋糕"巴特福奥克"
the Butterfinger Buttafuocos,
"乔伊"版"以及我本来以为卖不掉的
the Joeys, and even the Mary Jos,
"玛丽·乔"版 都统统卖光了呢
which I did not think would sell.
我把"南茜·克里根"重弄了一下
I reworked the smashed Nancy Kerrigans
然后改叫它"玛丽·乔"
and called it the Mary Jo.
姑娘们 我真替你们开心
Girls, I'm so happy for you.
我还记得我生意
You know, I remember when my business
刚开始蒸蒸日上那会
first started to take off.
我第一件事就是把我长大的那小村子
The first thing I did was to buy the little village
给买了下来
that I grew up in
然后一把火把它烧成灰烬
and then burn it to the ground!
我恨死他们
I was just so angry
当年不让我加入拉拉队了
they wouldn't let me be a cheerleader.
宝贝 那是电影《卡丽》的情节啦
No, baby, that was the movie Carrie.
你昨晚看的时候睡着了
You fell asleep watching it last night.
我以后不深夜看电影了
Oh. Yeah, I gotta stop watching movies late at night.
我因为这样 有一年
Once, for a whole year,
我以为是我陷害的兔子罗杰呢
I thought I framed Roger Rabbit.
我想找麦克斯自制小蛋糕的店主
I'm looking for the owners of Max's homemade cupcakes.
是我 真是名声传千里啊
Oh, that's me. Wow, word is really spreading.
有什么需要帮忙的吗
How can I help you?
你被传唤了
You've been served.
麦克斯 我被法院传唤[羞辱]了
Max, I just got served.
羞辱你的刘海吗 我肯定先从这开始羞辱起
Did he go after your bangs? 'Cause that's where I'd start.
这可是法律诉讼啊
This is a lawsuit.
上面写着 "麦隆·谢尔斯 也就是劫佩托
It says, "Max's homemade cupcakes is being sued
因在麦克斯自制小蛋糕店摔伤 而以
for injuries sustained in our shop by Myron Shales,
故意伤害罪起诉店主"
A.K.A. 'J. Petto.'"
麦克斯 是那个木偶男
Max, it's the puppet guy.
他要告咱们啊
He's suing us?
应该是我们告他很恶心...
We should be suing him for gross...
我不知道法律用词怎么说
I don't know what the legal words are
反正就是告他当个恶心人啦
but just for being gross.
我们承受不起被人告
We can't afford to be sued.
我们甚至请不起巴士广告上那个
We can't even afford the lawyer on those bus ads
一手拿小木槌一手抓只鸡的律师
who has a gavel in one hand and a chicken in the other.
希望两位对本店还满意
I hope everything was satisfactory.
请问两位女士还需要点什么吗
Can I get you ladies anything else...
比如强烈的职业道德如何
like a strong work ethic?
阿憨 不好玩啦 我们被人告了
Han, it's not funny. We're being sued.
好吧 文件给我看看
Okay, let me see those.
我在韩国曾学过法律
I studied law in Korea,
但是我没有读到毕业
but I never made it through graduation.
因为我意识到那不是我的兴趣
I realized it wasn't my passion,
所以我中途退出[拔出]了
and I pulled out.
有人知道你曾"进去"过吗
Did they know it was in?
我看看
Let's see...
没错 你们被告了
Yeah, you're being sued.
你念的哪间破学校 加州"陈述事实"大学吗
What law school did you go to, CAL State-the-obvious?
你是以最少高潮的成绩毕业的吗
Did you graduate magna come rarely?
我都说了 我退出[拔出]了
I told you, I pulled out.
但别担心 这种事故 开店的人
But don't worry, accidents like this happen
都常常碰到
in stores all the time.
所以一般开店做生意的都会买保险
That's why all businesses have insurance.
不是所有的店都有买
Well, not all businesses.
你们俩怎么能不买保险呢
How could you not have insurance?
你们得保护自己啊
You need to get protection.
我不是说戴避孕套的那种"保护"
And I'm not talking about condoms.
我们又不是傻子 阿憨
We're not idiots, Han.
我们曾讨论过是否要买保险
We had the insurance discussion.
我当时说 "麦克斯 我们得买保险"
I was like, "Max, we need insurance."
她说 "我们有钱买吗"
And she was like, "Do we have any money?"
我说"没有" 然后她就说
And I was like, "No." And she was like,
"那发生意外的几率是多少"
"What are the chances something will happen?"
我说 "百万分之一吧"
And I was like, "A million to one."
她就说 "我喜欢这种几率
And she was like, "I like those odds.
我们去买小熊糖吧" 我就说"好吧
Let's go get gummi bears." And I was like, "Okay.
这件事下次得再讨论吧"
But we'll talk about this at another time."
看 我们现在就在讨论啦
And here we are talking about it now.
记住 我们别无选择
Remember, we have no choice.
我们必须说服他撤销诉讼
We have to get him to drop this lawsuit.
3B 到了 这就是那个木偶男的公寓
Okay, 3B, here. This is the puppet guy's apartment.
你说他是木偶男 我说他是变态杀人魔
You say puppet guy, I say serial killer.
你说这是公寓 我说这是《梅根法案》
You say apartment, I say the brightest dot
网站上最高亮的住址
on the "Megan's law" website.
麦克斯 说这种话一点都不讨喜 心里要想着
Max, that is not charming. Stay on message.
-我们要讨喜 我们很抱歉 -我们喝醉了
- We're charming, we're sorry... - We're drunk.
至少我是
Well, I am.
不然你觉得我怎么扮得出讨喜样
How else do you think I'm gonna pull off charming?
咱们快进快出
Let's just get in and out of there.
那个木偶太吓人了
That puppet creeped me out.
我真不想再看见它
I don't want to have to see it again.
我还没醉到可以接受这场面
Oh, I am not drunk enough for this.
我喝再醉也接受不了这场面
I've never been drunk enough for this.
劫佩托在家吗
Is J. Petto home?
真让我大吃一惊
I'm kind of surprised.
我还以为他没有女朋友呢
I did not think he'd have a girlfriend.
你们好
Hello.
希望你们会喜欢伊薇特
Well, I hope you enjoyed meeting Yvette.
她会弹琵琶哦
She plays the lute, you know.
是啊 她非常可爱
Oh, yes, she was very charming.
也非常迷你 肯定会显得你的鸡鸡很大吧
And small. She must make your penis look huge.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
要讨喜 麦克斯 要讨喜
Charming, Max, charming.
我们顺路给你带了点小蛋糕过来
Hi, we just stopped by to bring you some cupcakes.
之前的事真的很抱歉
We feel so bad about what happened.
能进去坐会聊聊吗
Can we come in for a minute?
我没想到今天会有客人来
Um, well, I wasn't expecting company,
但是进来吧
but come in.
我们大伙正玩得欢呢
We're all just hangin' out.
这不诡异 这一点也不诡异
Oh, oh, this isn't weird. This isn't weird at all.
感觉好像进了死尸洗车机
It's like we're in a dead body car wash.
我曾做过个恶梦 梦到自己梦到这场景
I had a nightmare that I had a nightmare like this once.
先说好哦
Just so you know,
根据规定 我不能谈论这次诉讼的事
I'm not allowed to talk about the lawsuit.
真巧 我也不能谈论
Well, I'm not allowed to talk
自己此时此刻的真实感受
about how I really feel right now.
说到这次的诉讼 你看起来没事啊
Speaking of the lawsuit, you seem well--
身上没伤 这挺好的
you know, physically-which is great,
因为你在讼词里说 你手臂摔断
because the suit said you had a shattered arm
髋骨骨折
and a broken hip.
是啊 我告你们
Oh, yeah, I'm not suing you
不是为了我自己的手臂和髋骨
for my shattered arm and hip.
受伤的是皮埃尔
It's-it's for Pierre's.
我摔倒的时候 压坏了他的小身板
I crushed his little body when I fell.
他肯定是为了保护我 才舍身飞到我身后
He must have thrown himself under my body
给我当垫背的
to protect my fall.
《嗜血法医》 这有一个等你料理
Dexter, party of one.
为了让他恢复关节的正常活动 我每隔15分钟
I have to rotate his arm and hold it every 15 minutes
就得旋转他的胳膊 然后扶好固定
to get his full range of motion back.
这悬带就是为了固定 我知道他不是活人
That's what the sling's about. I know he's not alive.
真的吗
Do you?
他受伤了 我们真的非常抱歉
We're very sorry for his injury,
但这也太荒谬了吧
but this is absurd.
你不能因为你的木偶坏了就告我们啊
You can't sue us because your puppet broke.
当然能 这个木偶是我的谋生之道
Yes, I can. This puppet is my livelihood,
而且我给他投了大保
and he's heavily insured.
太棒了 连木偶都有保险 而我们俩活人却没有
Great, the puppet has insurance, and we don't.
-麦克斯 -什么
- Max! - What?
你们俩没有保险吗
You don't have insurance?
你们俩居然有钱做生意 没钱买保险
You have a business but no insurance?
我们不能上法庭 这会让我们倾家荡产的
Look, we can't go to court. It would wreck us.
这事能不能别通过法律途径
Can we leave the lawyers out of this
找一个更有创意的解决办法
and come up with a more creative solution?
一看你就是创意十足的人
I mean, you're clearly creative.
瞧 你还做了一个骷髅王
Look, you even made a skeleton king.
那不是什么骷髅王
That's not a skeleton king.
那是恶魔帕祖祖 邪恶王子
That's Pazuzu, prince of darkness.
那我就不妨直说吧
Let me just put this out there
因为这事得尽快解决
because we should really move things along,
而且我很害怕
and also, I'm afraid.
要多少钱你才愿意跟我们庭外和解
How much is it gonna take to make this go away?
你需要时间咨询下
Do you want to take a second to consult
你其中一位室友吗
with one of your roommates?
我好像看见有律师娃娃
I think I saw a lawyer doll.
他不是律师 他是餐厅领班
He is not a lawyer. He is a Maitre D'.
而且超能干的呢
And a damn good one!
你们女人就是不了解
You women just don't get it.
所以我才会通过网络电话
This is why I broke up with
跟我多伦多的女友分手
my Toronto-based girlfriend over Skype.
是吧
Right?
一千块 周一前给我
$1,000 by Monday.
手工雕刻的牵线木偶为娃娃的话...
hand-carved marionettes being dolls...
价格也会水涨船高
it goes up.
好 一千块 无其他附件条件[无线]
Fine, $1,000 and no strings.
-除了那些有附加"线"的... -麦克斯 闭嘴
- Except for the ones on all - Max, don't say it!
电影《娃娃谷》 《重返娃娃谷》
Valley of the dolls, Return to the valley of the dolls,
《鬼娃回魂》《鬼娃新娘》《你好 美娃》桃莱坞
Chucky, Bride of Chucky, Hello Dolly, Dollywood,
还有达赖[娃娃]喇嘛
And the Dalai Lama!
这些是我刚忍着的吐槽词
Those are the things I was holding in.
等等 还有"娃尔与奥兹"
Oh, wait-Doll and Oates!
现在怎么办
Now what?
我们周一前怎么筹到这额外的一千块
How are we gonna get 1,000 extra dollars by Monday?
等等 麦克斯 我们可以去酒吧
Wait, Max, we can go to that bar
运用下你特殊的天赋
and exploit your special gifts.
君要臣脱 臣不得不脱
If I have to strip, I have to strip.
不是脱衣舞酒吧啦 是嬉皮士的冷知识酒吧
Not that kind of bar, the hipster trivia bar.
不能跳脱衣舞就好吗 至少这样还有点尊严
Can't I just strip? At least I'd still have my dignity.
钱都在这了 一共一千块
It's all here. $1,000.
事情解决 诉讼撤销
So that's it. No more lawsuit.
老实说 事情还没解决
Actually, that's not it.
事实证明 还得再给五百块
As it turns out, we're gonna need 500 more.
为什么 难不成连环杀手协会和恋童癖协会
For what? Did your dues for the serial killer's union
今年都得在同一时间交年费吗
and the pedophile guild come up at the same time this year?
皮埃尔情况十分不妙
Pierre's in crisis!
就让他的精神科医生跟你们解释吧
But his psychiatrist could tell you more about that.
如果这公寓里有精神科医生
If there's a psychiatrist in this apartment
却没有把这疯子关起来 他的意见我才不信
who hasn't locked him up, I don't trust his opinion.
我是潘格罗斯医生
I'm Dr. Pangloss.
皮埃尔在你们店里 不仅摔伤了他的髋骨
Pierre broke more than his hip in your cupcake shop.
还摔垮了他的精神
He broke his spirit.
摔碎了他的梦想
He lost his dream!
他现在再也不想表演了
He no longer wants to perform.
现在他要把我们切成两半
This is where he cuts us in half
把我的上半身跟你的下半身缝在一起了
and sews my top to your bottom.
从好的方面看 就是前凸后翘腿子长
On the plus side, we'd look amazing.
没错 你们也听见了
Yeah, well, you heard it.
皮埃尔准备放弃他的艺术生涯
Pierre's ready to give up his art,
所以他需要多一点钱
and he needs a little more money.
休想 脑残娃娃迷 我们没有五百块
Forget it, puppet nuts. We don't have $500.
也无任何数量达五百的东西
We don't have 500 anything.
好好考虑下吧
Well, think about it.
我的茶壶烧开了 伊薇特
That's my tea kettle. Yvette!
算了 我自己来吧
Uhh! I'll do it.
我觉得你凶他一点用都没有
I'm not so sure the hostility is quite working,
不如你去走廊里等着吧
so why don't you go wait in the hall?
我会试着好好跟他讲讲理
And I'll try to talk some sense into him alone.
你是这世界唯一一个
You are the only person in the world
坚持要跟他单独共处一室的人
who would insist on being alone with this man,
不过随你吧
but okay.
拜托听我说 我们俩一穷二白
Please just listen. We are broke.
要再赚五百块 我们就得去跳脱衣舞了
To get any more money, we'd have to strip.
琪琪和拉娜一开始也是脱衣舞娘
Well, Gigi and Lana started off as strippers,
而现在她们可是女神游乐厅的红人 所以...
and now they're in the Folies Bergere, so...
人到中年 还当操偶师已经很怪
You know, even for a middle-aged puppeteer,
而你是怪中之怪
you're a freak.
法庭上见
See you in court!
没成功 他告定咱们了
Nothing. He's gonna sue us,
我们也没有其他锦囊妙计了
and we have no other tricks up our sleeve.
或许我的锦囊里没有 但请看我的外套
Well, maybe not my sleeve, but how about my coat?
-皮埃尔 -被老娘偷出来了
- Pierre? - Right there.
抱歉 本日闭店
I'm sorry, we're not open today.
我知道你把皮埃尔拿走了 快还给我
I know you took him. Give me back Pierre!
都说了本日闭店
We're not open.
我们发生了一场可怕的悲剧
We've had a terrible tragedy.
虽然不是我们本人 但我们的新朋友
Well, not us, but a new friend of ours
发生了可怕的意外 我们悲痛至极
had a gruesome accident, and we are just devastated.
你不会那么残忍吧
You wouldn't be that cruel.
放轻松 我当然不会这么残忍
Relax, I could never be that cruel.
但麦克斯就很难说了
But Max could.
瞧瞧谁来了 皮埃尔 是你的爱人 劫佩托
Look who it is, Pierre, your lover, J. Petto!
他不是同性恋
He's not gay.
他有女朋友的 她叫露露
He had a girlfriend named Lulu.
她曾是...法国国王的宫廷名妓
She was a--she was a courtesan in the court of a french king.
他们之所以分手 是因为露露跟伊薇特调情
They broke up over a brief flirtation she had with Yvette.
我知道他们不是活人
And I know they're not alive!
我们就遵守原本没附加条件约定 你看如何
Now, what do you say we stick to the original no-strings deal?
因为如果你不愿意 麦克斯会让你见识下
'cause if you don't, Max will show you
什么是真正的"没有线"[附加]
what "no strings" really means.
剪啊 来啊 有种你就剪断它
Do it! Go! Bring it!
反正我能重新绑 我可是这门手艺的大师
I can always re-string him. I'm a master of my craft.
没错 我们早知道你会这么说
Yes, we thought you'd say that.
你让我们别无选择 麦克斯
So you leave us no choice. Max...
什么 我...
What? I--
我不会改变主意的
I'm not changing my mind.
我要去找警察来
And I'm coming back with the police.
是我就不会叫警察哦
Oh, I wouldn't get the cops involved...
因为你的小娃娃现在...
Now that your boy here is in a...
抓奸在床 进退两难啊
compromising situation!
你好大的胆子
How dare you!
她做爱时可不喜欢戴套哦
And she does not like the feel of a condom!
你们俩变态
You two are sick!
我们才不会批评他们
Hey, we don't judge.
我们觉得无论这两名成年娃娃
We think whatever two consenting dolls,
或这三名成年娃娃做什么...
or maybe three consenting dolls do--
我肯定场面不会好看
and it's gonna be bad
他可是不硬则小 一硬惊人哦
'cause he's a grower, not a shower.
一旦这些照片放上网
And once a few of these pics are posted online,
你儿童派对的生意也会跟着完蛋
there goes your children's party business.
现在认输 我就把照片全删了
Now, call it quits, and you can delete these pics.
好 我认 你们赢了 你们赢了
Fine. Yes. Okay, you win. You win. You win.
口说无凭 我们不会再上当受骗了
Oh, we're not falling for your word again.
如果你想要回你的娃娃
If you want your doll back--
再说最后一遍 他不是娃娃
For the last time, he is not a doll!
我们要收到公证过的信件
Bring us a notarized letter saying
写明你放弃对麦克斯自制小蛋糕店
you release Max's homemade cupcakes
采取进一步的法律行动
of all further legal action,
然后我们就会把皮埃尔原封不动地还给你
and we'll give you back Pierre, perfectly intact.
当然 童贞还不了了
Minus his virginity, of course.
不过别担心 你的童贞一定还在
But don't worry, you'll still have yours.
好的 我会尽快回来的
Okay, I'll be back as soon as I can.
在残酷的木偶界混了三十年
Ugh, 30 years in the cutthroat world of puppets,
居然栽在两个卖蛋糕的疯婆子手上
and I'm undone by two crazy cupcake bitches!
你听到了吗 三十年啊
Did you hear that? 30 years?
追梦整整三十年 他还是一无所有
30 years of following his dream, and he's still broke?
我们也会这样吗 麦克斯
Is that gonna be us, Max?
我们的梦想跟木偶一样愚蠢吗
Is our dream just as stupid as puppets?
抱歉 皮埃尔 忘了你还在
Sorry, Pierre, I forgot you were here.
他好像睡着了
He's sound asleep.
"三人行"把他的体力榨干了
Three-ways really take it out of you.
给 帮她把衣服穿上 她得打车走人了
Here, dress her. She has to get a cab.
她宁愿回家睡自己的床
She'd rather sleep in her own bed.
你知道为什么我们不会变成他那样吗
And do you know why we're not gonna turn into him?
因为30年前 当劫佩托说
Because 30 years ago, when J. Petto said,
"我要成为一名操偶师"时
"I'm gonna be a puppeteer,"
他身边没有好友告诉他
he didn't have a best friend to tell him,
"你不该这样 这主意蠢透了"
"You shouldn't do that. It's a stupid idea."
你不像他 你有我来告诉你
And unlike him, you have me to tell you
哪些是蠢主意
when it's a stupid idea.
而你也会告诉我 不要用狼牙棒打自己
And I have you to tell me not to mace myself,
尽管我超级想试试是什么感觉
no matter how bad I want to know how it feels.
那蛋糕店不是蠢主意吗
So the cupcake shop isn't a stupid idea?
不是 而且生意刚要好转呢
No. And it's actually starting to take off.
因为蠢主意什么的 最合嬉皮士胃口了
'cause no one embraces a stupid idea like a hipster.
但麦克斯 我们真需要买保险了
But, Max, we do need insurance.
-可我们有钱买吗 -没有
- But do we have the money? - No.
那别人在店里摔倒的几率是多少
What are the chances someone else is gonna fall?
百万分之一
A million to one.
我喜欢这种几率
I like those odds.
这个裙子真可爱
You know, this is a really cute dress.
裙子算屁啊
Forget the dress.
你看他的小裤裤
Look at his cute pants.
我们真应该送给阿憨穿
We really should give them to Han.